Guide to the Stanford University, Department of Biology, Honors Theses
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Theses, Accession ARCH-1998-283
  - Lee, Michael Chun-chieh, Mechanism of Ion Secretion in the Calu-3 Human Airway Line., May, 1998 (Box 3)
  - Leung, Thomas, Characterization of the Biochemical Pathway Linking Cdk2 and the Activation of Cdc2-cyclin B at Mitosis in Xenopus Laevis., May, 1998 (Box 3)
  - Lin, Albert shincher, The role of phospholipids and disease severity in the macrophagic attack of RBC's and erythroid precursors in the thalassemic diseases, and the use of phenhydrazine-treated erythrocytes as a model for thalssemia., May, 1998 (Box 3)
  - Lin, Patty, BOD is an ovarian BH3 domain-containing pro-apoptotic Bcl-2 protein capable of dimerizing with anti-apoptotic Bcl-2 proteins., May 22, 1998 (Box 3)
  - Loh, Ern, Regulation of Neuron Activity in the Thalamus by Cholecystokinin., May, 1998 (Box 3)
  - Mann, Margaret Wing-Yan, The Nature of Signaling through the T Cell Receptor Affects the Regulation of T Helper 1 (Th1)/ Th2 Cytokine Profile by CYTRF., May, 1998 (Box 3)
  - Mehta, Umang, Use of the Enhanced Green Fluorescent Protein to Determine Cellular Localization of Peripheral Myelin Protein PMP22 In Cos7 Cells., May, 1998 (Box 3)
  - Modi, Biren P., Chemical Analyses of Biological Nanoenvironments.., May 1998 (Box 3)
  - Muller, Shaine A., Presence of Marfan Syndrome-causing mutation in family members who have only a partial phenotype suggests that other genetic variants contribute to Marfan Syndrome.., May 22, 1998 (Box 3)
  - Noh, Hansang, The regulating effect of insulin action on lipoprotein lipase expression in constitutively actice Ras, Raf-1, myristoylated/non myristoylated Akt mutants of different rat adipocyte cells.., May 22 1998 (Box 3)
  - O'Hanley, Jesse Rush, Importance of Specific Pyleonephritis-Associated Pili (Pap) Proteins in the Colonization of the Urniary Tract by Uropathogenic Escherichia coli.., May 1998 (Box 4)
  - Odom, Raanan, Two approaches to investigate the role of fibrillin-l in the pathogenesis of Marfan Syndrome.., May 1998 (Box 4)
  - Pagon, Garret D., Senescent Fibroblasts and the Role of Diminished Laminin-5 and Collagen VII in the Fragile Phenotype of Aging Skin.., May 1998 (Box 4)
  - Park, Aric Kihyun, Efficiency, efficacy, and toxicity of ex vivo transfection of antisense ICAM-1 ODN on cardiac allografts using pressure.., May 1998 (Box 4)
  - Patel, Maitraya, Ascorbic Acid Transport in Rat Hippocampal Cultures.., May 1998 (Box 4)
  - Peelle, Beau, Development of Systems for Studying Molecular Interactions Between Short Peptide Sequences and Screening of Retrovirus Expressed Peptide Libraries for Novel Dimerizing Peptides in a alian Cells.., May 1998 (Box 4)
  - Phillips, Paul, The N-terminal 687bp of the Immediate Early Gene 61 of Varicella-Zoster Virus (VZV) is Not Sufficient for Viral Replication., May 1998 (Box 4)
  - Potts, Brian Richard, The Mechanisms for Vascular Wound Repair In Vitro Using Human Dermal Microvascular Endothelial Cells.., May 22, 1998 (Box 4)
  - Rasouli, Alexandre, A Novel Mechanism of T Cell Subset Commitment: Analysis of the Transformation of Murine B Cells by Th2 Supernatant into Consistently Th2-Inducing Antigen Presenting Cells.., May 29, 1998 (Box 4)
  - Ripley, Beth, The effects of temperature on the jet escape response of the squid Loligo opalescens.., May 1998 (Box 4)
  - Robinson, Christopher, The Effect of Age on Thermoregulatory Vasconstriction and Sleep Architecture.., June 1997 (Box 4)
  - Sdrulla, Dan, The Effects of Adenosinergic Al Receptor Agonist Administratio on the Sleep Architecture and Intensity in the Developing Rat., May, 1998 (Box 4)
  - Shah, Sejal, Implications of the Excision of the Mu 1 Element from the mu 2 Site in Bronze 2 on Allelic Diversity, Excision Mechanisms, and Structure-function analysis., May 22, 1998 (Box 4)
  - Shih, Karen, Cytokine/ Chemokine Expression in Rat spinal cord contusion model., May 22, 1998 (Box 4)
  - Shpall, Rebecca Leanne, Interform inducible Nmi protein interacts with itself, IFP 35, and other novel protein.., May, 1998 (Box 4)
  - Tamaki, Tomoaki, Class I HLA-derived Immunosuppressive Peptide, B2702.84-75/75-84, Interacts with Vascular Cell Adhesion Molecule-1 (VCAM-1)., May, 1998 (Box 4)
  - Tang, Linda, Characterization of Ku binding to dsDNA.., May 22, 1998 (Box 4)
  - Thakarar, Sanjiv, Screen of ICAM-1 Coding Region ANtisense Oligonucleotides for Inhibition of Protein and RNA Expression to Locate Accessible Sites for Study of Induced Bulge Mechanism., May, 1998 (Box 5)
  - Thompson, Janelle R., Phenotypic characterization and phylogenic identification of a novel bacterial symbiont of Loligo opalescens., May, 1998 (Box 5)
  - Thu, Chris, Frog locomotion: ballistic assumptions and the determining factors of jumping distance in R. catesbeiana and R. pipens., May, 1998 (Box 5)
  - Tong, Candice, A targeted gene expression system for somatic hub cells of Drosophila melanogaster tests.., May 22, 1998 (Box 5)
  - Tubbesing, Victor, Cranial, Orbital Rete, and Red Muscle Vein Anatomy Indicate a High Degree of Endothermy in the Brain and Eye of the Salmon Shark, Lamna ditropis.., May, 1998 (Box 5)
  - Unger, Anne Violet, Role of the Egg Follicle Cells for DNA Photoreception in the Sea Squirt Ascidia ceratodes.., May 1998 (Box 5)
  - Vartanian, Shant, Oxidative Stress in Organotypic Cerebral Cortex Slice Cultures.., May 1998 (Box 5)
  - Vosganian, Gregory S., Isolation of Peptide Mimtopes to Hepatitis C Virus Envelope Protein E2 by a Phage Peptide Display System.., May 1998 (Box 5)
  - Wang, Angel, The Effects of Hyperglycemia on Human Aortic Endothelial Cells, via a PKC-Activated Signal Transduction Pathway.., May 22, 1998 (Box 5)
  - Wang, Frank, Age-Dependent Depressant Effects of Hypoxia in Rat Spinal Cord In Vitro: Role of Protein Kinase C.., May 1998 (Box 5)
  - Wang, Mark, Periprosthetic Tissue Reaction to Wear Debris from Metal versus Metal on Polyethylene Total Hip Replacement -- A Preliminary Study.., May 1998 (Box 5)
  - Yang, Chou, Incentive Contrast Effects on Saimiri sciureus Commsumatory Behavior and Pituitary-Adrenal Activity.., May 1998 (Box 5)
  - Yee, Kevin, ATtered protein kinase C sites on cystic fibrosis transmembrane conductance regulator regulatory domain result in decreased PKA-dependent channel function.., May 1998 (Box 5)
  - Yoon, John D., The Identification of Two Potential M-phase Targets in the Xenopus Cell Cycle: p140 and p116.., May 22, 1998 (Box 5)
  - Yung, Katherine C., Role of p53 in Expression of a Transfected Gene in Human Fibroblasts; Effects of UV Irradiation on the Plasmid and on the Host Cell.., May 1998 (Box 5)
  - Zapala, Matther Alan, A Comparative study of exotic and freshwater interactions in two Mediterranean type ecosystems: Southern Chile and Nothern California, with notes on the dissimilarity in Oncorhynchus mykiss populations.., May 22, 1998 (Box 5)
  - Zinggeler, Yves, Identification of CY, a new Gene Expressed Early in Mosoderm Development of D.melanogaster and a Candidate tinman Target Gene.., May 1998 (Box 5)
- Theses, Accession ARCH-1999-166
  - Alvarez-Saavedra, Ezequiel A., Idenitification and Characterization of SEG10, a Gene Expressed in Epidermal Stem Cells., May, 1999 (Box 1)
  - Alyeshmerni, Aviva M., The Effects of Estradiol on Neuron Differentiation and Survival: A Model of Estrogen Replacement Therapy in the Prevention of Alzheirmer's Disease., May, 1999 (Box 1)
  - Ambardar, Sheenie, Wild-Type Peripheral Myelin Protein 22 (PMP22) and Trembler-J Mustant PMP22 Affect the Cellular Distribution of Connexin32 via Formation of Heterodimes., May 13, 1999 (Box 1)
  - Arora, Anup, Characterization of Drosophilia Axin, an Inhibitor of Wingless Signaling., June, 1999 (Box 1)
  - Aslanian, Aaron, Post-Transcriptional Regulation of Gene Expression Under Hypoxia via the C-fos 3' Untranslated Region., May, 1999 (Box 1)
  - Barton, Kasey E., Niche Partitioning and Competition in Two Ant Communities., May 1999 (Box 1)
  - Bezdek, Trevor, 1. Evolutution and Analysis of DNA Classifiers. 2. The Role of the CcrM Methyltransferase in Caulobacter Crescentusthe cloning and characterization of the pstS Gene., May, 1999 (Box 1)
  - Bloom, Allyson K., Muscarinic Receptor Subtypes Mediating Neural Regulation of the PNMT Promoter., May 21, 1999 (Box 1)
  - Burns, Erik D., The effects of temperature on circadian rhythms of neuronal activity in the rat suprachiasmatic nucleus in vitro., May 1999 (Box 1)
  - Chan, Keith, Elucidating the regulation and function of CD30 expression on human T-cells.., May 1999 (Box 1)
  - Cheng, Karen D., An anatomical basis for visually guided auditory plasticity in the midbrain of the barn owl.., February 1999 (Box 1)
  - Chuong, Joseph P., Investigating the Mechanism of Tirapazamine Cell Kill and the Tirapazamine-Cisplatin Interaction in Saccharomyce cerevisiae., Spring 1999 (Box 1)
  - Conroy, Shannon M., Phosphorus limitation to nitrogen fixation in the cyanolichen, Pseudocyphellaria crocata.., May 1999 (Box 2)
  - DeWalt, Kevin C., Two-component regulatory systems in the Helicobacter pylori Genome, and their role in virulence.., May 1999 (Box 2)
  - Dunn, Casey, Temporal Dynamics of a Neotropical Nymphalid Butterfly Population., May 1999 (Box 2)
  - Fei, Matthew W., The elastase I enhancer stimulates expression of a reporter gene in a subset of humman pancreatic cancer cells.., May 1999 (Box 2)
  - Hammerman, Peter, Discovery of a Primate Model for Cystic Fibrosis.., May 28, 1999 (Box 2)
  - Herrington, Todd M., Control of spore differentiation in Myxococcus xanthus.., June 1999 (Box 2)
  - Howard, Daniel E., Identification of a transferable chaperonin-binding site in the von Hippel-Lindeau tumor suppressor protein.., May 1999 (Box 2)
  - Huang, Bryan J., Postprandial alterations in pulmonary and systemic vascular dynamics as measured by a single breath constant exhalation technique.., May 1999 (Box 2)
  - Irani, Neville, Concentration - Dependent EMF Effect on DNA Renaturation Kinetics.., May 1999 (Box 2)
  - Johnson, Alice V., Mutagenesis study of 3-hydroxy-3-methylglutaryl coenzyme-A reductase, the key enzyme in the cholesterol biosynthetic pathway, using the UT-2 cell system.., May 1999 (Box 2)
  - Knape, Jessica E., Temperature Adaptation of Neural Function among Intertidal Porcelain Crab Congeners from Different Therman Habitats.., May 21, 1999 (Box 2)
  - Kratz, Johannes Ruediger, Kinetics and Thermodynamics of Peptide/Class II MHC Complexes.., June 1999 (Box 2)
  - Laufik, Martin, Characterization of Drosophila melandogaster enhancer trap lines with lac-z expression in germ line stem cells., May, 1999 (Box 2)
  - Lee, Arthur, Axon Projection Patterns of 20 Proliferating 1st-Instar Neuroblasts in the Central Brain of Wild-Type 3rd-Instar Larvae of Drosophila melanogaster., June, 1999 (Box 2)
  - Leng, Theodore, Capillary Electrophoresis Coupled With RBL-2H3 Cells as a Single-Cell Biosensor., May, 1999 (Box 2)
  - Lew, Cuen Hong, Production of Plyclonal Antibodies Against a Candidate G-Protein Coupled Receptor In the Rat Cerebral Cortex., May, 1999 (Box 3)
  - Lin, Ines Chi-Ying, The Downregulation of Cell-Surface MHC Class I Expression On Cells Infected By Varicella Zoster Virus., May, 1999 (Box 3)
  - Lin, Richard, Ineffectiveness of Pre-Training In Reducing Variability of Fear Conditioning., June, 1999 (Box 3)
  - Lopez, Jacqueline M., Effects of Cortisol and Aging on the Performance of Squirrel Monkeys on an Object Retrieval/Detour Task., June, 1999 (Box 3)
  - Mac Dermed, Dhara, Mitochondrial enzymes involved in the loss of membrane potential in human tumor cells after aerobic Tirapazamine exposure., May, 1999 (Box 3)
  - Manoli, Devanand S., The NF-kb-specific k2 regulatory site mediates induction of TNF expression in macrophages following stimulation by LPS or inhibition of Calcineurin. (Box 3)
  - McCullough, Brendan, Identification and Characterization of BIRK, A Novel Protein Related to IRK1., May, 1999 (Box 3)
  - Mendoza, Dorinna, IL-2, IL-10, and Antibody Production by Human Splenocytes Following Exposure to VH4-34 Gene-Encoded Monoclonal Antibodies., May, 1999 (Box 3)
  - Mills, Christina E., The Use of Antisense Interference of S. typhimurium Virulence Genes to Construct Drug Conditional Mutants., May, 1999 (Box 3)
  - Mitra, Siddhartha, Purification and Characterization of the Second Nucleotide Binding Domain of The Cystic Fibrosis Transmembrane Conductance Regulator.., May 1999 (Box 3)
  - Narayanan, Divya, Characterization of the Multizenobiotic Resistance Protein in Developing Embryos Of the Sea Urchin, Lytechnius Pictus.., May,1999 (Box 3)
  - Pahm, Daniel T., Effects of Isoflurane at N-Methyl-D-Aspartate Synapses.., May 1999 (Box 3)
  - Peace, Ali, Biochemical Adaptation in Elasmobranch Lactate Dehydrogenase-A (A4-LDH) Orthologs.., May 1999 (Box 3)
  - Roeder, Adrienne H. K., Arabidopsis Thaliana Embryos with Mutations in the YODA gene are impaired in suspensor development.., May 1999 (Box 3)
  - Rogers, William M., Radiation Hybrid Mapping Human ESTs to Facilitate the "Genome Jumping" Strategy Employed to Reduce thecanarc-I Critical Region.., May 1999 (Box 3)
  - Rollins, Meghan, Medetomidine and Ketamine Anesthesia in Yellowfin Tuna (Thunnus albacares), Bonito (Sarda chiliensis) and Pacific Mackerel (Scomber Japonicus).., May 1999 (Box 3)
  - Sanghvi, Uma, Assessing Potential Risk Factors for Child Malnutrition in Rural Kerala, india.., May 1999 (Box 4)
  - Sdrulla, Andrei D., Control of Oligodendrocyte Differentiation by an ID Protein., May, 1999 (Box 4)
  - Shaikh, Abe, An NF-kB site Serves as an Enhancer REgion in Dnase Hypersensitive Sites 1,2 of the 3' Region of the translocated c-myc Allele in Burkitt's Lymphoma., May, 1999 (Box 4)
  - Sinha, Amit, Creation of Three novel mutations in Mycobacterium marinumL Characterization and Analysis of the Rv1217c, Rv1220c, and PPE homologues of Mycobacterium tuberculosis.., May, 1999 (Box 4)
  - Small, Kerrin, Molecular Mechanisms of Adaptive Gene Expression in the Teleost Fish Fundulus Heteroclitus.., May, 1999 (Box 4)
  - Somsouk, Lina, An NF-kB Site in the IgH Enhancer Deregulates bcl-2 Expression in t(14;18) Lymphomas.., May, 1999 (Box 4)
  - Toranto, Jason, Anatomical Study of the Hypobranchial Gland of Calliostoma Canaliculatum and the Neuronally Controlled Secretion of Yellow Stuff (YS).., May, 1999 (Box 4)
  - Tung, Joyce, Induction of ErbB Receptor Dimerization by EGF-like Ligands.., May 1999 (Box 4)
  - Wahlstrand, Ben, Correlating Habitat Temperature, Levels of Solute Inhibition, And Resistance to Proteolysis in Lactate Dehydrogenase A Orthologs.., May 1999 (Box 4)
  - Wang, David Stephen, The Mechanotransduction Pathway of Endothelial Oxidative Response to Cylic Stretch.., May 1999 (Box 4)
  - Wang, Sam C., Small Intestinal Brush Border Oligosaccharidase adaptation to Chronic Mesenteric Ischemia.., May 1999 (Box 4)
  - Wang, Sonya Grace, Subcellular Localization of cAMP-specific Phosphodiesterases.., May 1999 (Box 4)
  - Watson, Jana Joy, Distribution of sex and Age Class with Respect to Group Size and Stability of Humpback Whale (Megaptera Novaeangliae) Associations in the Southern Gulf of Maine During an Atypical Year, 1992.., May 1999 (Box 4)
  - Wong, Rachel, Cultural Preservation in Two Tibetan Children's Homes., 1999 (Box 4)
  - Yue, Brian W., Modification of Intrinsic Properties of Neurons Strongly Modulates Thalamic Network Oscillations.., March 1999 (Box 4)
  - Yusim, Anna, Application of Silicon Microphysiometry To Hippocampal and Cortical Tissue Slices:Characterizing metabolic effects of Hypoglycemia, cyanide, and HIV-1 glycoprotein gp120, in synergy with glucocorticoids.., May 1999 (Box 4)
  - Zagha, Edward, Mutational Analysis of Varcella-Zoster Virus (VZV) Open Reading Frames 64 and 69.., Spring 1999 (Box 4)
- Theses, Accession ARCH-2001-162
  - Adelman, Juliana, Isolation of macrophage inducible Salmonella typhimurium genes by differential fluorescence induction in a chemically defined media, pH5., May 2000 (Box 1)
  - Afarian, Hagop, The Effects of Early Rearing Conditions and Genetics on the Squirrel Monkey Prefrontal Cortex., May 2000 (Box 1)
  - Ahmad, Regina-Celeste, CD4+ T cell responses to the human cartilage autoantigen HCgp-39 epitope 298-313 in HLA-DR4 transgenic mice reveal residues important for immunogenicity., May 2000 (Box 1)
  - Alexander, Jes, eBoutiqueMaker: Constructing Automatically Updated Highly Specific Protein Motif Databases., May 2000 (Box 1)
  - Andersen, Erik, Analysis and Characterization of Mesoderm Migration and Heart Cell Fusion During Embryonic Development of Drosophila melanogaster., May 2000 (Box 1)
  - Arshi, Arash, Ewing's Sarcoma/PNET tumor cell lines express Her-2/neu which can be utilized as a target by redirected T cells., May 2000 (Box 1)
  - Behnke-Parks, William M., Fusion of Synthetic Vesicles Using RF Pulses, Chemical Reagents, and Fusagentic Proteins., May 2000 (Box 1)
  - Bollmann, Jyoti, The Perioperative Risk Factors Associated with Adult Respriatory Distress Syndrome Following Cardiopulmonary Bypass., June 2000 (Box 1)
  - Boyett, Jesse Marie, Somatostatin-immunoreactive interneurons contribute to lateral inhibitory circuits in the dentate gyrus of control and epileptic rats., May 2000 (Box 1)
  - Chiu, Lynn, Inhibition of Calpain Increases Cell Migration and Wound Healing via a Protein Kinase C Dependent Pathway in Human Dermal Microvascular Endothelial Cells., May 2000 (Box 1)
  - Cho, Min-Hee, Molecular mechanism of oligodencdrocyte induced sodium channel clustering in RGC axons., May 2000 (Box 1)
  - Chowdary, Meghna, MMP-9 activity levels in abdominal aortic aneurysms exposed to high blood flow., May 2000 (Box 1)
  - Comerford, Aurora J., An investigation of the p53- and p48-regulated repair of carcinogen-DNA adducts in mammalian cells., May 2000 (Box 1)
  - Doung, Yee-Cheen, Two novel SNARE proteins and structure-function studies of the membrane fusion complex., May 2000 (Box 1)
  - Dusek, Eva, Effects of Fishing Gear on Coral Reef Recovery in Kenya Following the 1998 El-Nino Induced Coral Bleaching., September 2000 (Box 1)
  - Ginsberg, Michael Lane, Isolation and cloning of single and double mutations in DnaK from Escherichia coli., May 2000 (Box 1)
  - Grantham, Theodore, Changes of Migration Patterns of Siberian and Baltic Barnacle Geese Branta leucopsis Staging in the German Wadden Sea., September 2000 (Box 1)
  - Hackett, Chris, Indentification and Characterization of Genes Affected by the dpiA Plasmid Destabilizer Gene in Escherichia coli that Compensate for its Destabilizing Effects on Plasmid pSC101., November 1999 (Box 2)
  - Ho, Jill, In Vivo Characterization of an Insult-Inducible Vector., May 2000 (Box 2)
  - Hu, Rollin C., Evidence for novel cannabinoid signaling in sperm: Activation of a receptor with homology to the mammalian CB1 cannabinoid receptor subtype by anandamide inhibits calcium influx via a cyclic-AMP independent mechanism in Strongylocentrotus purpuratus sperm., May 2000 (Box 2)
  - Jaiswal, Siddhartha, Identification of the Signaling Pathways Involved in Bcr/Abl Induced Transformation of Myeloid Cells., May 2000 (Box 2)
  - Jones, Matt, Development of Anti-Piwi Antisera and Germline Clonal Analysis Indicate that Piwi Functions in Embryonic Morphogenesis., May 2000 (Box 2)
  - Kao, Lily, Decreases in the potassium/chloride cotransporter KCC2 in chronically injured, epileptogenic neocortex., May 2000 (Box 2)
  - Kwok, Roberta, Identification of the Calcineurin Response Elements on the Murine Interleukin-12 p40 Promoter in Myelomonocytes., May 2000 (Box 2)
  - Lazar, Lawrence D., bFGF Promotes Proliferation and is Required for Cell Survival in E16 Cortical Rat Cultures., May 2000 (Box 2)
  - Lazarus, Brynne, Effects of environment, inheritance, and development on leaf shape in western poison oak (Toxicodendron diversilobum)., May 2000 (Box 2)
  - Lee, Suzanne E., Analysis of Genetic Control of Macrophage and T Cell Cytokine Production in Congenic B10.A and B10.BR Mouse Strains., May 2000 (Box 2)
  - Ling, Jennifer, Neurotrophin-3 is Efficacious in Preventing Axonal degeneration in the Peripheral Myelin-22 Peripheral Neuropathy., May 2000 (Box 2)
  - Ludington, Will, Population Genetics of Mastocarpus papillatus (Rhodophyta, Petrocelidaceae) Across the Point Conception Boundary on the California Coast., May 2000 (Box 2)
  - Meskell, Jillian Lee, Cell fate determination in the Caenorhabditis elegans vulva: identification and characterization of genes that function downstream of MAP kinase., November 1999 (Box 2)
  - Munir, Reema, Characterization of the Mineralocorticoid Receptor in a Teleost Fish, Haplochromis Burtoni., May 2000 (Box 2)
  - Novitski, Nancy, Studies fo the "alba" polymorphism in Colias butterflies., December 1999 (Box 2)
  - O'Mahar, Shannon Eileen, Laminin 6 and keratin 15; structural proteins involved in basement membrane formation and cell adhesion., May 2000 (Box 2)
  - Pasnick, Susan, Home-Range Analysis and General Description of the Fanalokas (Viverridae: Fossa fossana) of Vevembe, Madagascar., May 2000 (Box 2)
  - Patel, Ravi, The Effects of Glucorticoids on Glutathione Peroxidase and Associated Antioxidant Defenses in the Rat Hippocampus., May 2000 (Box 3)
  - Prakash, Saurabh, Mutations in a Potassium Channel Voltage Sensor Support Roles for Side Chain Volume and Valence in Activation., April 2000 (Box 3)
  - Reuter, John Edward, A Genetic Screen for Genes Involved in the Neuronal Morphogenesis of Drosophila Mushroom Bodies via Mosaic Analysis with a Repressible Cell Marker., May 2000 (Box 3)
  - Rivera, Kahealani Kamalia`okahokuloa, Characterization of Ex-Vivo Expanded gamma/delta T Cells Derived from CD8-/- Mouse Splenocytes., May 2000 (Box 3)
  - Saenz, Benjamin L., The Foraging Habits of the Plumbeus Vireo and Western Tanager in Northern Arizona Ponderosa Pine Forest., December 1999 (Box 3)
  - Scott, Hyman M., Mapping of Sites on HLA-DR (DR3) Important for Binding to HLA-DM., May 2000 (Box 3)
  - Singla, Sheela, Molecular Mechanisms of Calmodulin Trapping by CaM Kinase II., May 2000 (Box 3)
  - Slansky, Amy, Amelioration of experimental autoimmune encephalomyelitis during pregnancy., May 2000 (Box 3)
  - Talbott, Jason, Mechanisms of fluid secretion in the Calu-3 model of human serous cells., May 2000 (Box 3)
  - Toma, Jonathan, Administration of GAD65 Peptides Corresponding to the Immunodominant Epitopes Found in the NOD and NOD.PD Mouse Elicit a Delay in the Onset of IDDM., March 2000 (Box 3)
  - Vazquez, Jesus, Analysis of a Helicobacter pylori Shuttle Vector and Implementation of the Vector in Studying Motility Mutants., May 2000 (Box 3)
  - Wang, Bruce, Genetic Analysis of the Role of Drosophila Rho-Associated Kinase in Cellular Morphogenesis and Planar Polarity., May 2000 (Box 3)
  - Wang, Hank Simon, Mapping Domains in the Saccharomyces cerevisiae Nucleoporin Nup100 that bind Karyopherins., May 2000 (Box 3)
  - Wong, Emilia, In vivo testing of the hippocampal disinhibition hypothesis in epileptic Mongolian gerbils., May 2000 (Box 3)
  - Wu, Joanne, Isolation and immunogenicity of the measles matrix protein., May 2000 (Box 3)
  - Yu, Caroline Wei-tyng, Distribution of cobalt-permeable AMPA receptors in chronically injured rat cortex., June 2000 (Box 3)
- Theses, Accession ARCH-2002-094
  - Amirnazmi, Solmaz, Effects of P-glycoprotein mutations on ATPase activity in Sf21 insect cells., 2001 (Box 1)
  - Amitai, Nurith, The Dopaminergic System, Sleep and Motor Control in Canine Narcolepsy., 2001 (Box 1)
  - Anderson, Dorian, The roles of tanascin-C and the novel protein K12 in shaping neural progenitor cell-fate decisions in the mammilian cerebral cortex., 2001 (Box 1)
  - Anderson, Joe, Investigating the costal genes in Drosophila melanogaster Hedgehog signal transduction., 2001 (Box 1)